Class of 1999 Records, 1995-[ongoing]
Smith College Archives
Class of 1999 Records
1995-[ongoing]
Smith College. Class of 1999.
RG 80 UUID:10521971-6157-450f-ad3d-3b40cb900b93
1 box (.42 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1999.
The Class of 1999 was the 121st graduating class of Smith College.
The Class of 1999 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1999, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1999 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Announcements 1998-1999 (Box 2311, Folder 1)
- Class Cabinet 1998-1999 (Box 2311, Folder 2)
- Commencement 1999 (Box 2311, Folder 3)
- Commencement Speaker 1999 (Box 2311, Folder 4)
- Convocation Address 1999 (Box 2311, Folder 5)
- Groups 1998-1999 (Box 2311, Folder 6)
- House Representatives 1998-1999 (Box 2311, Folder 7)
- Ivy Day 1999 (Box 2311, Folder 8)
- President's Files 1996-1997 (Box 2311, Folder 9)
- Rally Day 1999 (Box 2311, Folder 10)
- Reunion 2000 (Box 2311, Folder 11)
- Scrapbook 1997-1998 (Box 2311, Folder 12)
- Senior Newsletter 1998-1999 (Box 2311, Folder 13)
- Who's Who 1995-1996 (Box 2311, Folder 14)